123together.com 2014-06-18

# 123Together Exchange Hosting Privacy Statement

123Together.com, a division of mindSHIFT Technologies, Inc., has created this privacy policy ("Policy") in order to demonstrate our commitment to customer privacy. Privacy on the 123Together.com web site (the "Site") is of great importance to us. Because we gather important information from our visitors and customers, we have established this Policy as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices.

This Policy applies to the 123Together.com Site. This Policy may not apply to mindSHIFT Technologies, Inc., Ricoh Americas Holdings, Inc. (“RAH”) or other mindSHIFT Technologies or Ricoh brands, divisions, web sites, products and/or services such as groupSPARK, among others, each of which may have their own privacy policies. We may post additional information if more details are needed to explain our privacy practices. 

**Information We Collect**

We receive and may store any information you enter on our Site or otherwise give to us. For example, we collect information from you when you place an order, create an account, call us with a question, provide a referral, write a review, or use any of our services. The information we collect from you includes things like:

  * Your name
  * Your mailing address
  * Your e-mail address
  * Your phone number
  * Your credit card number and other payment information
  * Credit application information, such as your Social Security Number
  * Demographic and lifestyle information, such as age, personal interests and product preferences

We require customers who register to use the services ("Services") offered on our Site to give us contact information, such as their name, company name, address, phone number, and email address, and financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, and the number of users within the organization that will be using the Services. You may also add additional personal information, such as title, department name, fax number, or additional company information, such as annual revenues, number of employees, or industry, when adding users. Customers can opt out of providing this additional information by not entering it when asked. Customers can update or remove their personal information at any time by logging into the Site and editing their Personal Information within Setup. Customers can view their updated profile to confirm their edits have been made.

We may also collect information you give us about other people such as name and address of referral(s).

_Hosted Data Provided by Customer_  
Customers will be using the Services to host data and information ("Data"). 123Together.com will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any Data except as provided in the Terms of Service, or as may be permitted in this Policy or required by law. 123Together.com does not claim ownership of any of the Data, including any text, data, information, images, photographs, music, sound, video, or other material, that is uploaded, displayed or stored as part of the customer’s Data. Individual records of Data may at times be viewed or accessed only for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issue, or suspected violation of the Terms of Service, or as may be permitted in this Policy or required by law. Of course, customers are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their user registration and password. See Terms of Service for full legal terms and conditions regarding your Data and our Services.

_Information from Other Sources_  
We may also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties that help us update, expand and analyze our records and identify new customers.

_Cookies and Other Automatic Information:_ _  
_ When you interact with the 123Together.com Site we strive to make that experience easy and meaningful. Like many other web sites, we also collect information through cookies and other automated means. Cookies are commonly used by web sites to save data on your computer. The information we collect from cookies may include your IP address, unique identifier, browser and device characteristics, referring URLs, and a record of your interactions with our Site. We use cookies to create a more personalized experience on our Site. 

When you come to our Site, our web server sends a cookie to your computer. Cookies are files that web browsers place on a computer's hard drive and are used to tell us whether customers and visitors have visited the Site previously.

Cookies come in two flavors: session and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during an online session. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you've closed your browser or turned off your computer.

123Together.com uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the system to uniquely identify you while you are logged in. This information allows 123Together.com to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies help us make sure you are who you say you are after you've logged in and are required in order to use the 123Together.com application. 123Together.com uses persistent cookies, that only 123Together.com (and its contractors and providers) can read and use, to identify the fact that you are a 123Together.com customer or prior 123Together.com Site visitor (whatever the case may be). We are especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, we do not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. Users who disable their web browsers' ability to accept cookies will be able to browse our Site but will not be able to successfully use our service.

In combination with other information we collect, cookies may facilitate the tailoring of advertisements and offers to you, sometimes in connection with interest-based advertising.  
To help us understand and enhance our interactions with visitors and customers to our Site, we may permit web analytics providers to collect information on our Site using automated tools like cookies or web beacons. We also may share personal information with those providers. We may have similar arrangements with interest-based advertisers. Interest-based advertising is covered in more detail below.

This website does not respond to do not track instructions from browsers.

_Public Forums:_ _  
_ Our Site may offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**   
We use the information we collect for things like:

  * Contact customers and prospective customers to discuss customer interest in our company and the Services that we provide 
  * Fulfilling orders and requests for products, services or information (including without limitation setting up Services for individuals and organizations, registering for Services in order to receive a user name and password, etc.)
  * Processing refunds
  * Tracking and confirming online orders
  * Delivering or installing products
  * Managing our loyalty program
  * Marketing and advertising products and services
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Establishing and managing your accounts with us
  * Communicating things like events, sweepstakes, promotions, surveys, newsletters and updates regarding the Services, company or partners 
  * Processing our credit card or loyalty MasterCard applications
  * Identifying you on our Site and tailoring advertisements and offers to you (both on our Site and on other web sites) based on your interactions with us whether in-person, over the phone, or via mail, e-mail or online.
  * Facilitating interactions with 123Together.com, mindSHIFT Technologies and others
  * Operating, evaluating and improving our business 

_Information Retention_  
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Retention and destruction of Data will occur as specified in the Terms of Service, including without limitation Cancellation Request. 

**How We Share the Information We Collect**   
123Together.com does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties.  
Ricoh Americas Holdings, Inc. (“RAH”) is the parent company of mindSHIFT Technologies, Inc. and as such, if you provide information to mindSHIFT Technologies or any of its businesses, divisions, subsidiaries or web sites owned or operated by mindSHIFT Technologies (including 123Together.com), this information may be combined or shared among current or future Ricoh Americas Holdings, Inc. (“RAH”) entities, including affiliates and subsidiaries, and will be governed by each of their privacy policies, as applicable.   
We may share your information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as:

  * Fulfilling orders and services
  * Delivering packages
  * Scheduling and performing installations
  * Servicing products
  * Maintaining our loyalty program
  * Sending marketing communications
  * Fulfilling subscription services
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Applying for credit cards & processing credit card payments 
  * Providing chat functions 

Sometimes we may be required to share personal information and/or Data in response to a regulation, court order or subpoena. We may also share information and/or Data when we believe it's necessary to comply with the law. We also may share information and/or Data to respond to a government request or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of 123Together.com, mindSHIFT Technologies, our customers, or others; to prevent harm or loss; or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity. 

We may also share personal information and Data in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event.

We may share personal information in connection with financial products or services related to our business such as private label credit cards. We also may share personal information in connection with co-branded product or service offerings. For example, when you apply for our credit card, we may share your personal information with our banking partners that issue the card. 

**How We Protect The Information We Collect**

We use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it. 123Together.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us. The Site uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during transport. SSL protects information you submit via our Site such as ordering information including your name, address and credit card number.  
In addition, our Site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Data under our control. When our Site is accessed using Netscape Navigator, or Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 5.0 or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology is designed to protect information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that Data is safe, secure, and available only to you. 123Together.com also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and hosts the Site in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology in attempt to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. Finally, 123Together.com provides unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a customer logs on. These safeguards are designed to help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of Data. See Terms of Service for full legal terms and conditions regarding your Data and our Services. 

**Transfer of Personal Information To Other Countries**

The server(s) hosting this web site and our databases may be outside the country from which you access this Site and may be outside your country of residence. Therefore, when you submit personal information or Data to us (whether directly or through this Site), your information and Data may be transferred to various countries around the world that may not guarantee the same level of privacy protection as your country and may be accessible to law enforcement and regulatory authorities according to the laws of foreign jurisdictions. By submitting your personal information or Data to us (whether directly or through this Site), you consent and agree that we may collect, store, use, process, transfer, and share your personal information as described in this Policy (including store, use and transfer your personal information outside Australia, Canada, Mexico and the European Economic Area). 

**Your Choices Regarding the Information We Collect**   
Visitors and customers may choose to:

  * Stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communications
  * Update and correct your personal information 
  * Request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum 

To do any of these, let us know by one of these methods:

  * Follow the directions in a marketing e-mail or direct mail or mobile communication that you receive from us.
  * Call 800-967-3924 with your request and current contact information.
  * Send an e-mail with your request and current contact information to [Support@123Together.com](mailto:Support@123Together.com)
  * Send a letter with your request and current contact information to: 

123Together.com  
309 Waverley Oaks Road   
Suite 301   
Waltham, MA 02452  
Our customers have additional choices:

  * If customers need to update or change registration information they may so by editing the user or organization record. To update a User Profile, log on to 123Together.com and update the appropriate information.
  * To discontinue the Service and to have Data returned, complete the service cancellation request form at <https://www.123together.com/cancel/Cancellation-Request.asp>

**Interest-Based Advertising**   
We may use third-party advertising companies to display ads when you visit our Site or other sites on the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to this Site and other web sites. We may also share personal information with these companies.In either case, the purpose is to provide ads about products and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Protecting Children's Privacy**   
We are committed to protecting children's privacy on the Internet and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**Third-Party Web Sites**  
The Site contains links to other web sites, many of which have their own privacy policies. 123Together.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. Customers and visitors will need to check the privacy policy statement of these others web sites to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential.

**Updates**   
We may need to update our Privacy Policy as 123Together.com and our customers grow and evolve. If we make significant changes to this Policy, we'll post a prominent message on our Site. 

**Have Questions?**

Questions regarding this Policy or the practices of this Site should be directed to 123Together.com by:  
Phone: 800-967-3924   
E-mail: [Support@123Together.com](mailto:Support@123Together.com)   
Address: 123Together.com  
309 Waverley Oaks Road  
Suite 301  
Waltham, MA 02452

**_Notice:_** **This policy has been updated to better enable customers to understand how their information is collected, used and shared.**

Last Updated: 1-31-14
